I am Pawan Kushwaha.  Karli I am working in
Fintech company and I am living in
Gurgaon.  I used to work in an insurance company.
I thought I would take term
insurance.  But I got married.  I had
my baby.  He also turned 2 years old.  Even then
I took term insurance.
But my cousin brother was 22 years old.
Hee pass away.  Then I got a fear.   I was
shocked that no, no, now I should
take term insurance to secure my
family.  Before buying insurance,
I compared different companies to see which
product was better.  So I
found ICICI Psial to be the best because it was the
most transparent.  I chose ICICI Ptial
's iProtect Smart Plus plan
because its benefits and features were quite
good.  My buying online insurance was
quite good.  Its website is very user
friendly.  The website also recommends
[music] your age and income, if you
put it in, it tells you both the premium payout and
coverage.  How long
should you take it?  One of the best things is this
with ICICI Bank.  [Music] Their claim
settlement ratio is quite good.  And their
claim gets settled quickly.  [MUSIC]
I travel every weekend.  Coming and going out by car.
So there was always a fear that
something might happen.  I'm Fully
Secure [Music].  By
taking iProtect Smart Plus Term Plan, my family
is also secure with financial protection.
[Music]